export const questionAnswers = [    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Anugul?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 753971 (Male: 383148, Female: 370823)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1236742 (Male: 637903, Female: 598839)      - Main Workers: 534934      - Marginal Workers: 325577 (with 176395 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 114459 (Male: 60414, Female: 54045)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Balangir?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 911714 (Male: 459962, Female: 451752)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1482402 (Male: 750954, Female: 731448)      - Main Workers: 624457      - Marginal Workers: 447121 (with 252441 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 175962 (Male: 86180, Female: 89782)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Baleshwar?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1379861 (Male: 702916, Female: 676945)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2194827 (Male: 1125776, Female: 1069051)      - Main Workers: 947281      - Marginal Workers: 407904 (with 234047 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 213188 (Male: 108437, Female: 104751)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Bargarh?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 837740 (Male: 420505, Female: 417235)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1464071 (Male: 747086, Female: 716985)      - Main Workers: 714619      - Marginal Workers: 412400 (with 231035 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 155163 (Male: 77111, Female: 78052)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Baudh?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 119769 (Male: 59955, Female: 59814)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 396789 (Male: 199013, Female: 197776)      - Main Workers: 192150      - Marginal Workers: 136373 (with 78753 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 41397 (Male: 21213, Female: 20184)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Bhadrak?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 917342 (Male: 463481, Female: 453861)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1406717 (Male: 708592, Female: 698125)      - Main Workers: 533350      - Marginal Workers: 198068 (with 115699 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 143149 (Male: 72823, Female: 70326)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Cuttack?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1421138 (Male: 725211, Female: 695927)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2641563 (Male: 1368342, Female: 1273221)      - Main Workers: 1125198      - Marginal Workers: 368919 (with 203925 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 278680 (Male: 144547, Female: 134133)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Debagarh?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 186656 (Male: 94010, Female: 92646)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 291790 (Male: 147070, Female: 144720)      - Main Workers: 131969      - Marginal Workers: 123033 (with 69768 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 28797 (Male: 14844, Female: 13953)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Dhenkanal?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 679286 (Male: 346221, Female: 333065)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1165010 (Male: 591462, Female: 573548)      - Main Workers: 462243      - Marginal Workers: 229147 (with 135538 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 122193 (Male: 64694, Female: 57499)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Gajapati ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 373302 (Male: 188460, Female: 184842)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 521039 (Male: 252252, Female: 268787)      - Main Workers: 291493      - Marginal Workers: 169529 (with 98089 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 44257 (Male: 19729, Female: 24528)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Ganjam?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 2154437 (Male: 1089824, Female: 1064613)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 3300862 (Male: 1643917, Female: 1656945)      - Main Workers: 1449394      - Marginal Workers: 956297 (with 522964 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 340460 (Male: 170847, Female: 169613)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Jagatsinghapur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 622063 (Male: 316245, Female: 305818)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1158414 (Male: 586555, Female: 571859)      - Main Workers: 454561      - Marginal Workers: 177338 (with 100750 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 135901 (Male: 70047, Female: 65854)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Jajapur ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1072015 (Male: 544132, Female: 527883)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1748729 (Male: 880258, Female: 868471)      - Main Workers: 648398      - Marginal Workers: 226780 (with 132525 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 185483 (Male: 95642, Female: 89841)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Jharsuguda  *?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 169943 (Male: 86199, Female: 83744)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 252376 (Male: 131613, Female: 120763)      - Main Workers: 115137      - Marginal Workers: 57861 (with 15284 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 0 (Male: 0, Female: 0)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kalahandi?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 419142 (Male: 212400, Female: 206742)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1442619 (Male: 722292, Female: 720327)      - Main Workers: 641367      - Marginal Workers: 514629 (with 293679 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 149616 (Male: 70977, Female: 78639)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kandhamal?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 468227 (Male: 235035, Female: 233192)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 651813 (Male: 319903, Female: 331910)      - Main Workers: 297641      - Marginal Workers: 270835 (with 149184 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 63443 (Male: 30102, Female: 33341)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kendrapara?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 842840 (Male: 423516, Female: 419324)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1356148 (Male: 662481, Female: 693667)      - Main Workers: 513148      - Marginal Workers: 199001 (with 113957 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 169309 (Male: 86502, Female: 82807)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kendujhar?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1075577 (Male: 543244, Female: 532333)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1687680 (Male: 853102, Female: 834578)      - Main Workers: 735677      - Marginal Workers: 496668 (with 277490 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 143972 (Male: 71506, Female: 72466)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Khordha ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1182643 (Male: 613791, Female: 568852)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2259140 (Male: 1180252, Female: 1078888)      - Main Workers: 980130      - Marginal Workers: 231488 (with 139532 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 204845 (Male: 108647, Female: 96198)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Koraput ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 828514 (Male: 414842, Female: 413672)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1262315 (Male: 627529, Female: 634786)      - Main Workers: 644902      - Marginal Workers: 430868 (with 244119 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 108756 (Male: 48412, Female: 60344)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Malkangiri?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 384219 (Male: 192277, Female: 191942)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 522358 (Male: 262372, Female: 259986)      - Main Workers: 284236      - Marginal Workers: 181694 (with 104665 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 46495 (Male: 20199, Female: 26296)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Mayurbhanj?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1551133 (Male: 796267, Female: 754866)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2336068 (Male: 1159814, Female: 1176254)      - Main Workers: 1003992      - Marginal Workers: 959762 (with 549408 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 212916 (Male: 103185, Female: 109731)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Nabarangapur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 356745 (Male: 181726, Female: 175019)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 480319 (Male: 241043, Female: 239276)      - Main Workers: 223859      - Marginal Workers: 237826 (with 65284 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 0 (Male: 0, Female: 0)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Nabarangapur ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 407080 (Male: 202829, Female: 204251)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 574717 (Male: 286356, Female: 288361)      - Main Workers: 239190      - Marginal Workers: 241539 (with 206749 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 89672 (Male: 40966, Female: 48706)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Nayagarh ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 532963 (Male: 275420, Female: 257543)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 939866 (Male: 484950, Female: 454916)      - Main Workers: 364462      - Marginal Workers: 178899 (with 102739 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 113702 (Male: 61089, Female: 52613)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Nuapada ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 361555 (Male: 181395, Female: 180160)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 545460 (Male: 271748, Female: 273712)      - Main Workers: 239479      - Marginal Workers: 232619 (with 134288 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 64549 (Male: 30335, Female: 34214)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Puri?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 924505 (Male: 469367, Female: 455138)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1691285 (Male: 859009, Female: 832276)      - Main Workers: 702666      - Marginal Workers: 220708 (with 138059 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 185576 (Male: 95090, Female: 90486)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Rayagada?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 596029 (Male: 301263, Female: 294766)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 879664 (Male: 428546, Female: 451118)      - Main Workers: 410419      - Marginal Workers: 327766 (with 195761 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 72607 (Male: 29919, Female: 42688)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Sambalpur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 596253 (Male: 301214, Female: 295039)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1032096 (Male: 523834, Female: 508262)      - Main Workers: 522464      - Marginal Workers: 268848 (with 149925 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 98822 (Male: 50266, Female: 48556)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Subarnapur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 365637 (Male: 183616, Female: 182021)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 564733 (Male: 290591, Female: 274142)      - Main Workers: 262966      - Marginal Workers: 173485 (with 96301 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 64886 (Male: 33220, Female: 31666)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Sundargarh ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1240152 (Male: 631011, Female: 609141)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2026814 (Male: 1034753, Female: 992061)      - Main Workers: 889903      - Marginal Workers: 518448 (with 274978 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 163970 (Male: 81163, Female: 82807)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of  Coimbatore?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 751617 (Male: 383411, Female: 368206)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2083363 (Male: 1035671, Female: 1047692)      - Main Workers: 1266699      - Marginal Workers: 94919 (with 82306 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 391332 (Male: 191928, Female: 199404)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of  Nagapattina?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 423684 (Male: 214061, Female: 209623)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 904148 (Male: 439311, Female: 464837)      - Main Workers: 415601      - Marginal Workers: 151723 (with 130041 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 169696 (Male: 83980, Female: 85716)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Ariyalur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 198761 (Male: 102297, Female: 96464)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 410627 (Male: 197496, Female: 213131)      - Main Workers: 228469      - Marginal Workers: 71084 (with 59792 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 87911 (Male: 44275, Female: 43636)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Chennai ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1034866 (Male: 529274, Female: 505592)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2818870 (Male: 1412245, Female: 1406625)      - Main Workers: 1461775      - Marginal Workers: 147478 (with 129419 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 457228 (Male: 222031, Female: 235197)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Cuddalore?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 688815 (Male: 353841, Female: 334974)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1474330 (Male: 730990, Female: 743340)      - Main Workers: 723494      - Marginal Workers: 272390 (with 229750 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 241130 (Male: 120245, Female: 120885)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Dharmapuri ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 414602 (Male: 224528, Female: 190074)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 832280 (Male: 419234, Female: 413046)      - Main Workers: 562350      - Marginal Workers: 80428 (with 68090 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 140615 (Male: 68235, Female: 72380)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Dindigul ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 532863 (Male: 275166, Female: 257697)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1233565 (Male: 607292, Female: 626273)      - Main Workers: 811132      - Marginal Workers: 111742 (with 97192 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 236331 (Male: 117230, Female: 119101)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Erode?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 496247 (Male: 258756, Female: 237491)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1325694 (Male: 655564, Female: 670130)      - Main Workers: 929678      - Marginal Workers: 64713 (with 56534 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 290671 (Male: 144509, Female: 146162)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kancheepuram?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 957845 (Male: 491629, Female: 466216)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2355413 (Male: 1178868, Female: 1176545)      - Main Workers: 1221034      - Marginal Workers: 245580 (with 208457 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 365113 (Male: 179295, Female: 185818)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kanniyakumari ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 435909 (Male: 221196, Female: 214713)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1076076 (Male: 527489, Female: 548587)      - Main Workers: 485885      - Marginal Workers: 101936 (with 82865 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 227569 (Male: 111030, Female: 116539)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Karur ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 250052 (Male: 129875, Female: 120177)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 608807 (Male: 296662, Female: 312145)      - Main Workers: 424417      - Marginal Workers: 27197 (with 23429 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 132026 (Male: 63741, Female: 68285)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Krishnagiri?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 525433 (Male: 276792, Female: 248641)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1037249 (Male: 522437, Female: 514812)      - Main Workers: 633726      - Marginal Workers: 110093 (with 94303 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 161890 (Male: 80776, Female: 81114)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Madurai?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 759342 (Male: 393766, Female: 365576)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1747473 (Male: 867641, Female: 879832)      - Main Workers: 1018213      - Marginal Workers: 142725 (with 122398 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 304936 (Male: 148195, Female: 156741)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Namakkal?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 425685 (Male: 226735, Female: 198950)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 977994 (Male: 483130, Female: 494864)      - Main Workers: 699816      - Marginal Workers: 44780 (with 39938 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 216685 (Male: 103966, Female: 112719)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Perambalur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 153087 (Male: 80374, Female: 72713)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 307478 (Male: 147657, Female: 159821)      - Main Workers: 212989      - Marginal Workers: 35200 (with 31967 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 62140 (Male: 31720, Female: 30420)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Pudukkottai?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 429364 (Male: 219596, Female: 209768)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 895743 (Male: 436303, Female: 459440)      - Main Workers: 542932      - Marginal Workers: 98967 (with 85759 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 164370 (Male: 81441, Female: 82929)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Ramanathapuram?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 358784 (Male: 184196, Female: 174588)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 760061 (Male: 380077, Female: 379984)      - Main Workers: 412275      - Marginal Workers: 93551 (with 83014 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 132575 (Male: 66312, Female: 66263)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Salem?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 881496 (Male: 472144, Female: 409352)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1979505 (Male: 997880, Female: 981625)      - Main Workers: 1319698      - Marginal Workers: 103903 (with 88926 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 378440 (Male: 184930, Female: 193510)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Sivaganga?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 338268 (Male: 173817, Female: 164451)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 750603 (Male: 368480, Female: 382123)      - Main Workers: 390024      - Marginal Workers: 127944 (with 110084 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 151975 (Male: 76399, Female: 75576)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thanjavur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 612289 (Male: 311792, Female: 300497)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1364231 (Male: 657397, Female: 706834)      - Main Workers: 714044      - Marginal Workers: 113820 (with 99012 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 259295 (Male: 126376, Female: 132919)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of The Nilgiris?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 180505 (Male: 91204, Female: 89301)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 436373 (Male: 212324, Female: 224049)      - Main Workers: 283970      - Marginal Workers: 25280 (with 21847 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 71305 (Male: 32788, Female: 38517)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Theni?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 316525 (Male: 166780, Female: 149745)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 710448 (Male: 351992, Female: 358456)      - Main Workers: 452634      - Marginal Workers: 49220 (with 42775 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 133821 (Male: 63077, Female: 70744)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thiruvallur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 903681 (Male: 464335, Female: 439346)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2213832 (Male: 1107028, Female: 1106804)      - Main Workers: 1118647      - Marginal Workers: 234029 (with 196455 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 314765 (Male: 152628, Female: 162137)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thiruvarur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 317996 (Male: 160839, Female: 157157)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 724242 (Male: 353792, Female: 370450)      - Main Workers: 350875      - Marginal Workers: 104432 (with 91753 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 133079 (Male: 66717, Female: 66362)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thoothukkudi ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 450847 (Male: 228916, Female: 221931)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 968860 (Male: 476741, Female: 492119)      - Main Workers: 559861      - Marginal Workers: 70467 (with 62911 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 199194 (Male: 92608, Female: 106586)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruchirappalli?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 676154 (Male: 346428, Female: 329726)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1548743 (Male: 759107, Female: 789636)      - Main Workers: 928085      - Marginal Workers: 104855 (with 90648 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 301977 (Male: 146324, Female: 155653)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tirunelveli ?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 789157 (Male: 402691, Female: 386466)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1710338 (Male: 839939, Female: 870399)      - Main Workers: 1098089      - Marginal Workers: 131658 (with 109945 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 349038 (Male: 161693, Female: 187345)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruppur?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 554987 (Male: 283008, Female: 271979)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1484039 (Male: 741504, Female: 742535)      - Main Workers: 994012      - Marginal Workers: 75258 (with 65905 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 264900 (Male: 132136, Female: 132764)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruvannamalai?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 641570 (Male: 329907, Female: 311663)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1367281 (Male: 677426, Female: 689855)      - Main Workers: 819593      - Marginal Workers: 216273 (with 186201 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 259118 (Male: 126559, Female: 132559)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Vellore?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 1042324 (Male: 534415, Female: 507909)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 2205504 (Male: 1089604, Female: 1115900)      - Main Workers: 1182843      - Marginal Workers: 267943 (with 220434 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 377563 (Male: 177901, Female: 199662)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Viluppuram?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 939829 (Male: 482188, Female: 457641)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1894537 (Male: 941523, Female: 953014)      - Main Workers: 1068018      - Marginal Workers: 358881 (with 306877 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 332676 (Male: 166729, Female: 165947)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {      "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Virudhunagar?",      "answer": "As the region has the following demographics:  - Age Group <19:      - Total: 500010 (Male: 256164, Female: 243846)      - Main Occupation: Students      - Suggested Schemes: Post Office Savings Account (SB).  - Age Group 20-59:      - Total: 1101465 (Male: 544576, Female: 556889)      - Main Workers: 728379      - Marginal Workers: 75432 (with 64294 engaged for 3-6 months)      - Suggested Schemes: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY).  - Age Group 60+:      - Total: 200394 (Male: 95452, Female: 104942)      - Main Occupation: Retired or part-time work      - Suggested Schemes: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS).  Additional Recommendations:      - For Farmers: PM-KISAN for income support, PMFBY for crop insurance, SHC for soil health improvement.      - For Women: Mahila Samman Savings Certificate for financial security and empowerment."    },    {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of  Coimbatore?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 751617 (Male: 383411, Female: 368206)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 2083363 (Male: 1035671, Female: 1047692)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 391332 (Male: 191928, Female: 199404)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of  Nagapattina?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 423684 (Male: 214061, Female: 209623)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 904148 (Male: 439311, Female: 464837)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 169696 (Male: 83980, Female: 85716)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Ariyalur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 198761 (Male: 102297, Female: 96464)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 410627 (Male: 197496, Female: 213131)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 87911 (Male: 44275, Female: 43636)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Chennai ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 1034866 (Male: 529274, Female: 505592)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 2818870 (Male: 1412245, Female: 1406625)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 457228 (Male: 222031, Female: 235197)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Cuddalore?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 688815 (Male: 353841, Female: 334974)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1474330 (Male: 730990, Female: 743340)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 241130 (Male: 120245, Female: 120885)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Dharmapuri ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 414602 (Male: 224528, Female: 190074)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 832280 (Male: 419234, Female: 413046)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 140615 (Male: 68235, Female: 72380)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Dindigul ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 532863 (Male: 275166, Female: 257697)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1233565 (Male: 607292, Female: 626273)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 236331 (Male: 117230, Female: 119101)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Erode?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 496247 (Male: 258756, Female: 237491)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1325694 (Male: 655564, Female: 670130)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 290671 (Male: 144509, Female: 146162)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kancheepuram?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 957845 (Male: 491629, Female: 466216)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 2355413 (Male: 1178868, Female: 1176545)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 365113 (Male: 179295, Female: 185818)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Kanniyakumari ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 435909 (Male: 221196, Female: 214713)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1076076 (Male: 527489, Female: 548587)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 227569 (Male: 111030, Female: 116539)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Karur ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 250052 (Male: 129875, Female: 120177)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 608807 (Male: 296662, Female: 312145)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 132026 (Male: 63741, Female: 68285)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Krishnagiri?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 525433 (Male: 276792, Female: 248641)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1037249 (Male: 522437, Female: 514812)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 161890 (Male: 80776, Female: 81114)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Madurai?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 759342 (Male: 393766, Female: 365576)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1747473 (Male: 867641, Female: 879832)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 304936 (Male: 148195, Female: 156741)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Namakkal?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 425685 (Male: 226735, Female: 198950)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 977994 (Male: 483130, Female: 494864)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 216685 (Male: 103966, Female: 112719)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Perambalur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 153087 (Male: 80374, Female: 72713)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 307478 (Male: 147657, Female: 159821)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 62140 (Male: 31720, Female: 30420)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Pudukkottai?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 429364 (Male: 219596, Female: 209768)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 895743 (Male: 436303, Female: 459440)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 164370 (Male: 81441, Female: 82929)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Ramanathapuram?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 358784 (Male: 184196, Female: 174588)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 760061 (Male: 380077, Female: 379984)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 132575 (Male: 66312, Female: 66263)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Salem?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 881496 (Male: 472144, Female: 409352)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1979505 (Male: 997880, Female: 981625)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 378440 (Male: 184930, Female: 193510)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Sivaganga?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 338268 (Male: 173817, Female: 164451)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 750603 (Male: 368480, Female: 382123)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 151975 (Male: 76399, Female: 75576)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thanjavur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 612289 (Male: 311792, Female: 300497)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1364231 (Male: 657397, Female: 706834)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 259295 (Male: 126376, Female: 132919)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of The Nilgiris?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 180505 (Male: 91204, Female: 89301)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 436373 (Male: 212324, Female: 224049)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 71305 (Male: 32788, Female: 38517)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Theni?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 316525 (Male: 166780, Female: 149745)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 710448 (Male: 351992, Female: 358456)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 133821 (Male: 63077, Female: 70744)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thiruvallur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 903681 (Male: 464335, Female: 439346)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 2213832 (Male: 1107028, Female: 1106804)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 314765 (Male: 152628, Female: 162137)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thiruvarur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 317996 (Male: 160839, Female: 157157)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 724242 (Male: 353792, Female: 370450)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 133079 (Male: 66717, Female: 66362)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Thoothukkudi ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 450847 (Male: 228916, Female: 221931)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 968860 (Male: 476741, Female: 492119)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 199194 (Male: 92608, Female: 106586)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruchirappalli?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 676154 (Male: 346428, Female: 329726)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1548743 (Male: 759107, Female: 789636)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 301977 (Male: 146324, Female: 155653)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tirunelveli ?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 789157 (Male: 402691, Female: 386466)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1710338 (Male: 839939, Female: 870399)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 349038 (Male: 161693, Female: 187345)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruppur?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 554987 (Male: 283008, Female: 271979)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1484039 (Male: 741504, Female: 742535)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 264900 (Male: 132136, Female: 132764)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Tiruvannamalai?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 641570 (Male: 329907, Female: 311663)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1367281 (Male: 677426, Female: 689855)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 259118 (Male: 126559, Female: 132559)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Vellore?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 1042324 (Male: 534415, Female: 507909)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 2205504 (Male: 1089604, Female: 1115900)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 377563 (Male: 177901, Female: 199662)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Viluppuram?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 939829 (Male: 482188, Female: 457641)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1894537 (Male: 941523, Female: 953014)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 332676 (Male: 166729, Female: 165947)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      },      {          "question": "What are the schemes suitable for the district of Virudhunagar?",          "answer": "Population: Age <19: - Total: 500010 (Male: 256164, Female: 243846)\n      -, Age 20-59: - Total: 1101465 (Male: 544576, Female: 556889)\n      -, Age 60+: - Total: 200394 (Male: 95452, Female: 104942)\n      -. Recommended Schemes: Age <19: Post Office Savings Account (SB), Age 20-59: Recurring Deposit (RD), Public Provident Fund (PPF), Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY), Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY), Age 60+: Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS), Additional: PM-KISAN, PMFBY, SHC, Mahila Samman Savings Certificate."      }    ]  
